# Ali Mozhdehi Fard

GitHub | in LinkdIn | ⊕ Personal Website | ✓ Gmail | 1 +989159141336

## SUMMARY

I have a master in Civil Engineering in field of Water and Hydraulic engineering also I am research assistant with a demonstrated history of working in the higher education industry; skilled and interested in computational fluid dynamics and numerical modeling.

# Work Experience

**English Teacher** 2020 - Present

Teaching English to students and IELTS candidate not only satisfy my passion for teaching but also help me sharpen my language skills.

#### Scrum master and Python developer

2020 - Present

As a Scrum master I learn to lead a team and be familiar with agile coaching techniques.

Teacher's Assistant 2018 - 2020

I got a lot of experience and skills as a lecturer and mentor for hydraulic Engineering students, such as communication, teaching, and documenting skills.

# Projects

## Academic Project

Developing supervised and unsupervised machine learning algorithms.

learning Finite difference method and solving partial differential equations.

Improving my skills in finite element method and developing program by FORTRAN and MATLAB.

I worked with HEC-RAS, FLOW-3D, and ANSYS for modeling different hydraulic problems.

Structural design of concrete and steel structure using ETABS

#### EDUCATION

Master of Science, Civil Engineering at Babol Noshirvani University of Technology 2017 - 2020

2012 - 216 Bachelor of Science, Civil Engineering at Sadjad University

#### Publications

Mozhdehi Fard Ali, Rahmani Firoozjaee Ali (Feb. 2020). "The effect of numerical parameters in discrete least-squares Meshless method in the analysis of water hammer phenomenon". In: 18th National Hydraulic Conference of Iran.

Mozhdehi Fard Ali, Rahmani Ali (Feb. 2022). "Modeling of water hammer with fluid-structure interaction in elastic pipelines using discrete least squares". In: International Journal of Pressure Vessels and Piping.

#### SKILLS

Programming Skills FORTRAN, Python, MATLAB

Software Skills FLOW-3D, HEC-RAS, Open Foam, Ansys, ETABS, LATEX, Microsoft Office

Last updated: October 16, 2022